{
    "subject": "resource/Elena_Gerhardt",
    "predicate": "property/shortDescription",
    "object": "German classical singer",
    "human_readable": "Elena Gerhardt's short description is that she is a German classical singer.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7208410501480103,
            "question": "What kind of singer is Elena Gerhardt?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6619713306427002,
            "question": "Can you name some famous German classical singers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5197678804397583,
            "question": "What nationality is Elena Gerhardt?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4469430148601532,
            "question": "What is Elena Gerhardt's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40886321663856506,
            "question": "Where is Elena Gerhardt from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3953566551208496,
            "question": "What are some characteristics of classical singing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.322369784116745,
            "question": "What genre of music does Elena Gerhardt perform?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25043442845344543,
            "question": "Is Elena Gerhardt known for performing opera?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24130624532699585,
            "question": "What style of music is considered 'classical'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20357169210910797,
            "question": "What training is typically required to become a classical singer?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Elena Gerhardt's short description is that she is a German classical singer.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1645_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What style of music is considered 'classical'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1645_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Elena Gerhardt known for performing opera?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1645_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music does Elena Gerhardt perform?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1645_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1645_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1645_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1645_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1645_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1645_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1645_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1645_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1645_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1645_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1645_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have more triples to evaluate!  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information about Elena Gerhardt, indicating she was a German mezzo-soprano singer associated with the singing of German classical lieder. This supports the statement that Elena Gerhardt is described as a German classical singer."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}